{"response_code":0,"results":[{"category":"Science & Nature","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"A defibrillator is used to start up a heartbeat once a heart has stopped beating.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Science & Nature","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What is the primary addictive substance found in tobacco?","correct_answer":"Nicotine","incorrect_answers":["Cathinone","Ephedrine","Glaucine"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Musicals & Theatres","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"Who serves as the speaker of the prologue in Shakespeare&#039;s Romeo and Juliet?","correct_answer":"Chorus","incorrect_answers":["Montague","Refrain","Capulet"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"How much did the indie game &quot;Cave Story&quot; cost when it was first released in 2004?","correct_answer":"$0 USD","incorrect_answers":["$5 USD","$10 USD","$15 USD"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Which of the following colors does the Zombie eyes glow in the &quot;Nuketown&quot; map in &quot;Call of Duty: Black Ops II&quot; Zombies mode?","correct_answer":"Yellow and Blue","incorrect_answers":["Yellow and Red","Red and Blue","Blue and White"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"In the Kingdom Hearts series, which is not an optional boss you can fight?","correct_answer":"Master Yen Sid","incorrect_answers":["Sephiroth","Julius","Kurt Zisa"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What nuts are used in the production of marzipan?","correct_answer":"Almonds","incorrect_answers":["Peanuts","Walnuts","Pistachios"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Shang Tsung is a playable character in Mortal Kombat XL.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Musicals & Theatres","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What is Jean ValJean&#039;s first prisoner number?","correct_answer":"24601","incorrect_answers":["9430","1729","32769"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Who is Sora&#039;s Nobody in Kingdom Hearts?","correct_answer":"Roxas","incorrect_answers":["Riku","Kairi","Mickey"]}]}